(由TurboScribe轉錄。 升級到無限以移除此訊息。) Hey, guys.
Hey.
So, what do you think?
About what?
What?
Are you kidding?
Okay, I'll give you a hint, I'll give you a hint.
Eyes.
No, no.
Your eyes.
No.
Chandler's eyes.
I got glasses.
You always had glasses.
No, I didn't.
Are you sure?
Didn't you used to have a pair?
They were really round and burgundy and they made you look kind of...
Feminine.
Yes.
No.
Sweetie, I think the glasses look great.
They make you look really sexy.
Really?
Yeah.
You didn't think I used to wear glasses, right?
Of course.
You know what?
I'll be there for you When the rain starts to pour I'll be
there for you Like I've been there before I'll be there for you
So there for you So
what do you guys want for an engagement present?
That's okay, Pheebs.
We're not having a party or anything, so you don't have to get
it If someone wants to give us a present, we don't want to
deprive them of that joy Oh, you know what you should get them?
One of those little portable CD players Oh, I already have one Not
unless someone borrowed it and left it at the gynecologist Yeah, and by
someone, she means Joey Hey, I know what I want What we want,
honey No, no, you don't want this I want to have your grandmother's
cookie recipe You mean the chocolate chip cookie recipe?
Uh-huh, yeah You mean the one that my grandmother made me swear
on her deathbed that I would never let out of our family?
Giant people say the craziest things I've wanted it for years.
I'm just going to make cookies for my children Break my heart Oh,
all right Okay, I'm going to be the mom who makes the world's
best chocolate chip cookies Our kids are going to be fat, aren't they?
Ahoy!
Hey, how's the boat?
Great, I'm really getting into this sailing stuff Oh, so you finally took
it out of the marina, huh?
Why would I do that?
It took three guys to get the thing in there Well, if you
don't sail your boat, what do you do on it?
That's great.
It's a great place to just kind of sit, hang around, drink a
few beers, eat some chips Well, it's good that you finally have a
place to do that You know, Joey, I could teach you to sail
if you want You could?
Yeah, I've been sailing my whole life When I was 15, my dad
bought me my own boat Your own boat?
What?
He was trying to cheer me up.
My pony was sick You
know what I was thinking?
What?
Nothing.
I just like to go like this Hey Chandler, what are you doing
tonight?
Uh, why?
Do you have a lecture?
No, why?
Then free as a bird.
What's up?
Uh, my dad wants to know if you want to play racquetball with
us Wow, that's great.
Dad must really like you.
He doesn't ask just anyone to play Yeah, and he didn't really ask
for you.
He asked for Chauncey I assumed he meant you Well, did you correct
him?
No, I thought it would be more fun this way That is so
cool.
Maybe this is something you could do every week Yeah, or you could
sit with him on the front porch and make sure no one steals
the trash cans He does that every week too Oh, just so you
know, you have to let him win.
He hates to lose Oh, no problem.
Maybe I'll play with my left hand You're not a lefty?
Does anybody know me?
What's wrong, Phoebe?
I just went to my old apartment to get you the cookie recipe
and that stupid fire burned it up No!
Why didn't you make a copy and keep it in a fireproof box
and keep it at least 100 yards away from the original?
Because I'm normal That was the one legacy my grandmother left me and
I know you wanted it as an engagement present We have to get
you an engagement present?
Don't worry about it, Phoebs No one got me an engagement present Okay,
here.
I don't have the recipe, but here I wish you health and happiness
An old cookie?
This is what happens when you don't register for gifts I made a
batch and I froze it and this is the only one left We
can't accept this Why not?
Because it's gross No, wait.
I think I can figure out the recipe from this cookie I do
stuff like this at work all the time Really?
Yeah, I think I can do it Oh, yay!
Okay, Ross, we owe you a present Two!
I've been engaged twice!
Look at this clown Just because he got a bigger boat, he thinks
he can take up the whole river Get out of the way, jackass!
Who names their boat Coast Guard, anyway?
That is the Coast Guard What are they doing out here?
The coast is all the way over there Joey, just ignore the boats,
all right?
We're not finished with our lesson yet All right Okay, I'm just going
to go over the basic points one more time Are you ready?
Come on, Rach.
Not again.
I got it, okay?
Let's start sailing And I want to go over there where that boatload
of girls is Yo-ho!
Oh, okay.
Is that what you want to do?
You want to go over and give a little shout-out to the
old hot chicas, huh?
Okay Let's do that, Sailor Joe Quick question, though What's this called?
Uh, boat row Wrong How do you get the mainsail up?
Uh, rub it?
No What do you do if I say we are coming about?
I'd say, come again?
No, no, I know this one, I know this one Time's up.
Now you're dead And deaf!
Okay, you just go on and make your little jokey jokes But if
you do not know what you are doing out at sea, you will
die at sea Am I getting through to you, Sailor?
Don't just say yes.
This isn't a game Joe, you could really get hurt out here Okay,
so do you want to pay attention or do you want to die?
I want to make a ship to shore call to Chandler All
right, I definitely taste nutmeg You do?
You don't?
Well, that's the difference between a professional and a layman That and
arrogance Hey Hey, how was sailing?
I don't want to talk about it Now, you could at least save
me a whole cookie No, no, no, no, no, no Women are mean
What is that?
Now the only thing that's left of my grandmother's legacy is this crumb
I wish you a long and happy marriage Hey Hey, how was it?
Well, I had a great time Um, Chauncey, on the other hand I
will tell the story It was going great I let him win We
were bonding He even said that I could call him dad And what
did he ask you, not to call him?
Daddy All right, look, here's the story Well, we had just finished playing
racquetball And we were going to take a steam I walk into the
steam room And it's really steamy So I take off my glasses And
that's when it happened Guys?
Over here Have a seat, son Hey!
Oh, Chandler, I can't believe it I know You gave my father a
lap dance Why did they put so much steam in there?
Because otherwise they'd have to call it the room room Why, okay, why?
Why did that have to happen?
Come on, it's not that big a deal Not that big a deal
There...
There was touching of things Chandler, I know you wanted to bond with
my dad But did you really have to bond to that part?
Listen, I'm sure that dad doesn't care He probably thought this was really
funny He'll be telling this story for years I don't want him to
tell this story for years Oh, but he will He still tells the
story about how Monica Tried to escape from fat camp I wasn't escaping
Then how'd you get caught in the barbed wire?
I was trying to help out a squirrel You were trying to eat
it If that is your father calling to tell this story Then the
marriage is off Come on Hello I'm sorry, you have the wrong number
Okay, I'll call you later, dad, I love you Bye All right, I'm
off to see your dad Whoa, whoa, aren't you a little overdressed?
Yeah, and you better make sure he tips you this time Look, I
figured I would try to convince him not to tell the story anymore
And I figured the best way to do that was face to face
And by face, I don't mean his lap And by face, I don't
mean my ass Hey, are you getting Monica and Chandler an engagement present?
I don't know You know, they didn't get us anything Thank you Hey,
hey Well, hello So when are we getting back out on the water,
matey?
Well, I don't know the boat way to say this, but never Why
not?
Because you're mean on the boat I was just trying to teach you
Well, lesson learned, Rachel is mean Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep, yep I
remember when she took me out on her dad's boat She wouldn't let
me help out at all Oh, excuse me, I wanted you to help
But you couldn't move your arms because you were wearing three life jackets
You have to respect the scene Look, Joey, I'm sorry if you thought
that was mean But I gotta tell you something, that was not mean
Hey, my father is mean He used to yell at me all the
time on the boat, and it was horrible I was just being a
really good teacher Does a good teacher say, put down the beer pin,
Ed?
Well, does a good student drink seven beers during his first lesson?
Six and a half You knocked that last one out of my hand,
remember?
Yeah, I didn't want you to get hit by the boom Well, it
hit me anyway And it would have hurt a lot less if I'd
have finished that last beer Oh, you know what?
I'm sorry I will try to tone it down and, uh, stop yelling
You won't boss me around anymore?
I won't boss you around And you'll be nice?
And I'll be nice And you'll be topless?
Joey!
You want me to learn Okay, here's batch 22 Ah,
maybe these will taste like your grandmother's This has a little bit of
orange peel, but no nutmeg Let's give it a shot I've not made
this many cookies since I was in the ninth grade What was that
for, like a bake sale?
No, just a Friday night These are pretty good Yeah, but not as
good as batch 17 Which one was that?
The ones we had right after you almost threw up Oh yeah, batch
17 was good I did not like batch 16 Okay Are there any
more from the good batch?
Because we could just work off of those Well, yeah, I think there's
one from batch 17 left Batch 16, 16 people, get out of the
way!
Okay, Joey, honey, you're doing really good All right, now I'm just going
to need you to step to the port side Remember how we talked
about the port side?
Oh yeah Right?
No It's left, sweetie, but that's okay, that's a tough one Why don't
you just say left?
Okay, go to the left!
The left!
Huh?
Just sit over there!
Okay, okay, keep yelling again, see that?
No, no, no, no, no, very quiet, said with love, no, no Well,
you know what?
Since I'm here, I think I'm going to have me a little beer
on the port side See what I did there?
Okay, Joey, we're luffing a little bit, so will you tighten up the
Cunningham?
All right, well, you just said a bunch of stuff I don't know,
man Joey, come on, you just went over this!
Oh, you know, when we did that was when that bird was flying
overhead with the fish in his mouth Did you see it?
It was gross No!
All right, I did not see the bird, I did not see the
fish I did not see the piece of styrofoam that was shaped like
Mike Tyson I did not!
Because I was trying to teach you how to sail a boat Which
obviously is an impossible thing to do All right, that's it, you're yelling
and I don't see you taking your top off I quit!
What do you mean you quit?
You can't quit!
Why not?
Because you're not finished yet and I won't have it Greens do not
quit!
Greens?
I'm a Tribbiani and Tribbianis quit!
Oh my God, wait, did I?
I just said Greens don't quit, didn't I?
Did I just say Greens don't quit?
Yes, yes!
You did and you're still yelling at me!
No, no, no, I'm not yelling at you, I'm just yelling near you
Oh God, Joey, oh, I'm my father, oh my God, this is horrible
I've been trying so hard not to be my mother, I did not
see this coming Oh, Joey, I'm sorry, I'm so sorry I just wanted
you to learn Hey, I did learn Really?
Yeah, come on It's okay I know what a mainsail is I know
to duck when the boom comes across I know port is right Left
Damn it What are we going to do with all these cookies?
Joey You know, I bet it would actually make my grandma really happy
to know that we're trying to figure out her recipe I bet she's
looking up at us and smiling right now Looking up?
Oh, yeah, no, she was really nice to me, but she's in hell
for sure Well, I've tried everything, I give up I guess I'm not
going to be the mom who makes the world's best chocolate chip cookies
I do make the best duck confit with broccoli rabe Kids love that,
right?
Oh, Phoebe, come on, isn't there any relative that would have the recipe?
What about your sister?
Oh, no, no, no, I made a promise to myself that the next
time I would talk to Ursula is over my dead body And that's
not happening until October 15th, 2032 That's the day you're going to die
See, darn it, I've got shuffleboard that day That's what you think Well,
I mean, what about friends of your grandmother's?
Wouldn't they have the recipe?
Well, you know, I may have relatives in France who would know My
grandmother said she got the recipe from her grandmother Nestle Toulouse What
was her name?
Nestle Toulouse Nestle Toll House?
You Americans always butcher the French language Phoebe, is this the recipe?
Yes!
Oh I cannot believe that I just spent the last two days trying
to figure out that recipe and it was my cupboard the whole time
I know You see, it is stuff like this which is why you're
burning it now So you understand, I'd feel a lot more comfortable if
you didn't tell people what happened You know, I'm a little embarrassed about
it I understand completely There's nothing more horrifying than embarrassing
yourself in front of your in-laws As a matter of fact, when
I started dating Judy, I was unemployed and her father asked me what
I did for a living and I told him I was a lawyer
What did you do when they found out?
They never did So if you ever see me giving them legal advice,
just nod along Shall we?
So, I guess we wear swimsuits in here Well,
Joey, I hate to admit it Your way of sailing is a lot
more fun Yeah, yeah Hey, why don't you give a pull on that
rope?
Oh, we're not sailing Just pull on it All right Sandwiches!
What else?
Here you go Thank you Oh, wow What are you doing?
Sorry Don't hold it like that, you're letting all the good stuff fall
out Oh Careful!
You're wasting good pastrami!
Oh my God I'm my dad!
I'm my dad!